BLAIR WARNER

blairthedesigner.com blairthedesigner@gmail.com 425.524.7910

I am a User Experience Designer who puts people first. With a background in graphic design and years of teaching experience, I am no stranger to problem solving. I love to make meaningful experiences and hopefully can make the world a better and happier place. I also enjoy drawing, practicing Japanese, and I have an unhealthy addiction to denim.

EXPERIENCE

ENGLISH TEACHER

Ibaraki, Saitama and Tokyo, Japan 4.2006 - 3.2008 / 4.2011 - 3.2016 Taught English and about different cultures in a total of 22 different elementary and junior high schools. I created classroom materials, presentations, and activities for classes.

GRAPHIC DESIGNER / LETTERPRESS PRINTER

Bell'Invito Letterpress Studio - Dallas, TX 2.2009 - 8.2009 Design of couture stationery design, web graphics for the company site, and file preparation for die creation. Operated of nineteenth century letterpresses for printing a die-cutting, as well as assembly of stationery.

ASSISTANT GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Standard Deluxe, Inc. - Waverly, AL 5.2005 - 2.2006 Logo and t-shirt design as well as file preparation for screen printing. Maintenance of website and web store images and database.

LEGAL ASSISTANT

Davis, Bingham & Hudson, Attorneys at Law - Auburn, AL 8.2000 - 5.2005 Receptionist duties, document dispersal, package delivery, and process server.

EDUCATION

UX Design Immersive General Assembly - Seattle, Washington 2016

Bachelor of Fine Arts in Graphic Design Auburn University - Auburn, Alabama 2000 - 2005

SKILLS

Heuristic Evaluation Comparative Analysis Competitive Analysis Task Analysis Affinity Diagram Concept Map Personas User Stories Storyboard User Journey User Scenario User Flow Site Map Prototype Sketch Wire frame Navigation

TOOLS

Sketch
Axure
Omnigraffle
Balsalmiq
Invision
Illustrator
Photoshop
InDesign
Office